Yes, I am Daikoku Yuzuki of Team Orca and
I am Director Murahoshi of Ukka. I am Yuzuki Daikoku, a member of Team Shachi, and Murahoshi Murahoshi, a board member of Uguka.
Last time, we had a lot of personal stories, and we had a lot of otaku talk in common.
I think we had a lot of fun with our geek talk,
We are going to appear together in an event.
Thank you very much.
We will be performing at Tokyo Kinema Club on September 6.
We will be performing at "Tokyo Yakan Land vol.3 Rose of Uguisudani" on September 6 at Tokyo Kinema Club.
Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm so happy.
I'm with Suzuki.
Isn't this the first time? We're doing this kind of event together, aren't we?
That's right.
It's called Tokyo Yakan Land,
Various idols from Stardance and other groups will come together.
I'm looking forward to it.
We're from completely different groups.
It will be live entertainment with singing, acting, and talking.
Volume 1 was held in March and Volume 2 in June at Harajuku Louido.
Since this is the third time, I would like to introduce some of the participating members.
First of all, I, Yuzuki Daikoku, the president of the team, and Uka Urashi-chan.
Then, Sakura Seta from X Shoujo-tai.
Waka Yasumori from Iginari Tohoku, Miyu Fujitani, Ibuki Mita from Crown Pop, and...,
Nitruna, Kana Harima, Kurumi Hori, Mai Haruna, and Aika Kinui of Scene On,
And former Takarazuka and current idol YouTuber Maya Ayaha will also be performing.
Amazing! I'm so excited!
I'm very nervous.
I'm really looking forward to this event, where we can transcend the boundaries between the two groups and create a new event together with other non-staplers!
This is my third time to Tokyo Night Land, and it's been a little bit more exciting than the first time.
It has been a hot topic since the first one. One of our members, Ruri Aoi, has performed at both events,
When I talked to Ruri, she told me that she sang some songs other than the ones on Stapler, and even acted in a play,
I also heard a lot of her stories about what she did with her glasses. So you are complete, Ayaka-chan.
Oh, muscularisombic. No, it's easy. It's amazing. Do you usually do any acting? I have been in a couple of dramas with the Uguka group, but only a little bit. I haven't done so much acting that I can say I have done much acting. I have performed on stage a few times,
I am looking forward to seeing how it will turn out.
Singing? You can sing. You can sing.
It's not often that we get to sing a song from a group other than our own for our fans, is it?
That's right. I guess it would be a solo live performance, or a solo live performance for the birthdays of the members.
I'm sure the fans would be happy too. We have a lot of songs.
Are there any songs you want to sing?
Recently, I like a lot of Disney songs from the land of dreams.
Under the Sea, for example. I also have a song called "Ana" from "Anna and the Snow Queen 2.
There is a song called "Ana" from the second part of "Anna and the Snow Queen," and I like that song.
It's expensive, but I could sing it. It sounds like it would go really well. Really?
You and the Snow Queen? I've heard of you and the Snow Queen's "First Time in My Life" and I'd like to sing it,
I have a longing to sing it. Oh, you can do it, can't you? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh no, Disney's music, Disney's music. It's on the screen, isn't it?
I don't have a chance to sing Disney songs, you know. I don't have a chance to sing Disney songs. You sing at your birthday or something?
You've never sung? No, not yet. Then, many people will hear it for the first time.
Many people will hear it for the first time. If you do something like that. If we do.
What songs would you like to sing? I like idols, and I also like the music of my mother's generation,
I like idols, and I also like the nostalgic music of my mother's generation, and I often sing that kind of music at birthday parties.
I would like to try a different genre of music. I feel like if I go to a karaoke place, I can put in a lot of my favorite songs, but I would like to try something different.
I would like to try a different kind of song.
Well, you haven't quite decided what kind of songs you are going to sing yet, have you?
That's right.
I'm getting a little nervous now.
But, you know, roses. Your roses.
Oh no, it's already a rose.
A rose.
A rose, that means.
It's so strong, isn't it?Isn't it kind of gory already?
Maybe so. I don't know.
I have no idea. It's just an image.
Image-wise.
What would you do? What if it's a heavy song?
But I'll do my best.
That's all right.
I'll see you again...a different one. I'm looking forward to it. When you decided to perform, did you get any reaction from fans or members?
Ruri, who has performed twice, gave me a lot of support and said, "Please do your best, Ryu-chan. There were people who said it was quite unexpected.
I don't really want to be a part of a group, or even a unit, because I don't really want to be a part of a unit. I don't really want to be a part of a group. I have never been a part of a unit before, so Tokyo Yakan Land is the first time for me to be a part of something like this, outside of a group. I want to do my best. I have been contacted by many people, including Hana-chan from AmeFlash, who performed at the previous event.
I've heard from many of the past performers.
I heard from the past performers that they thought I was a bit of a surprise, but that I was having a lot of fun, and that I was getting along really well with everyone.
I heard that. That's what I'm looking forward to the most.
That's what I'm looking forward to the most. I don't know, it's a little bit like this.
I'm not very good at performing on stage or in plays, but I'm looking forward to it,
I'm not very good at the stage or the play itself, but I really like the process of getting to know each other and creating a piece of work.
It is a wonderful thing, isn't it? So when I heard that we could get along with each other
I was really looking forward to it. I really think we might end up going to Puroland.
I really want to go. It might happen soon. I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it!
I'm looking forward to seeing what it's going to be like. If you don't come here, you'll be missing out.
I definitely want you to come. So I hope everyone will come to see the Uguisudani rose.
For more information on tickets and other details, please visit the official Twitter page of Kettle and Idol. So, Niz-chan, can you give us your enthusiasm and a message for everyone?
Yes, I will be performing in Tokyo YakanLand vol. 3. This will be the first time for me to perform on a stage like this, where there will be acting, singing, and talking, so I am very nervous, but I will do my best to bring a good time to everyone. Please come and see us. Please come and see us.
I will do my best to bring you an enjoyable time. This place called Tokyo Kinema Club...
I've been to Tokyo Kinema Club before, and I've been a part of the Orca Festival there.
It's a very nice stage.
There is a stage, a staircase, and then another staircase to the top.
I'm looking forward to seeing you again on the stage and in various places.
I really feel that we can show you our various appearances on the stage
I really feel that we can show various aspects of ourselves on the stage.
Talking, singing, acting, and so on.
I can enjoy all of them in one event.
I can enjoy all of them in one event. I think it's really rare to be able to enjoy all of them in one event and to be able to transcend the boundaries between groups.
We will not let you regret it, so we would be very happy if you could come. Please look forward to it.
I'm glad to hear that. I had a chance to talk with Riju before this nighttime event.
I was happy too.
We talked about Sanrio and so on.
We talked about Sanrio.
Even between rehearsals.
I hope we can get to know each other better and better.
I'm looking forward to it.
I look forward to seeing you.
So, I am looking forward to seeing you all.
My partners so far are Yuzuki Daikoku of Team Orca and
and Mr. Murahoshi, the director of Uguka.
Thank you very much.
Please come to Yokohama Amber.